Guide to the Washington State Federation of Teachers Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1947-2006; 1977-2006; 2201-008; 5 cubic feet 5 boxes
  - Legislative Testimony (Box-folder 2)
  - LegisLetter file (Box-folder 2)
  - Lobby Day, 1991 (Box-folder 2)
  - Lobby Day, 1992 (Box-folder 2)
  - Lobby Day (Box-folder 2)
  - LWTC-ULP (Box-folder 2)
  - WEA/WFT Co-op papers (Box-folder 2)
  - Organizing Opportunities (Box-folder 2)
  - Organizing Material (Box-folder 2)
  - Organizing/Puyallup PARAS (Box-folder 2)
  - Ortblad Case, 1998 (Box-folder 2)
  - Peninsula College 2-93 (Box-folder 2)
  - Personnel File legislation (Box-folder 2)
  - Pierce Negotiations Proposal (Box-folder 2)
  - Political Action Workshop (Box-folder 2)
  - PR Campaign (Box-folder 2)
  - PSE Superior Court, 1993 (Box-folder 2)
  - PT disparity, 1997 (Box-folder 2)
  - PT equity (Box-folder 2)
  - PT dues (Box-folder 2)
  - PT provisions (CCS) (Box-folder 2)
  - PT equity campaignh (Box-folder 2)
  - PT lawsuit/wages (Box-folder 2)
  - PT meeting (Box-folder 2)
  - PT organizing project (Box-folder 2)
  - PSE/WFT talks (Box-folder 2)
  - Public Employee Collective Bargaining (Box-folder 2)
  - Reasonable Assurance Bill (Box-folder 2)
  - Release Time, 1997 (Box-folder 2)
  - Restructuring Task Force (Box-folder 2)
  - Running Start (Box-folder 2)
  - SB 6306 Tenure (Box-folder 2)
  - Voc. Ed. (Box-folder 2)
  - Technology (NK) (Box-folder 2)
  - Tenure Memos (Box-folder 2)
  - Tenure Reviews SHB 5878 (Box-folder 2)
  - Training Committe, 1996 (Box-folder 2)
  - ULWU Anti-Disaffiliation Campaign (Box-folder 2)
  - UCWU Election, 1999 (Box-folder 2)
  - UCWU Election, 1999 (Box-folder 2)
  - UFE Due Process (Box-folder 2)
  - Unemployment (Box-folder 2)
  - ULI Washington, 1998 (Box-folder 2)
  - AFT: WEA CC Council, 1986 (Box-folder 3)
  - Classified Council, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Community College Council, 1994 (Box-folder 3)
  - Minutes CC Council, 1994/1995 (Box-folder 3)
  - AFT Computer IBM (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Com College Council, 1996 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Com College Council, 1997 (Box-folder 3)
  - CC Council Agenda/Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 3)
  - Port Orchard Federation of Teacheres Local 807 (Box-folder 3)
  - Edmonds Federation of Teachers Local 1690 (Box-folder 3)
  - Aberdeen Strike, 1972 and 1977 (Box-folder 4)
  - Aberdeen Federation of Teachers (Box-folder 3)
  - Bremerton Federation of Teachers Local 336 (Box-folder 3)
  - Western correspondence (Box-folder 3)
  - Buckley (Box-folder 3)
  - Rainier School Federation of Service and Teaching Aides, AFT #3390 (Box-folder 3)
  - Classifeid Survey (Box-folder 3)
  - Classified Meetings, 1997 (Box-folder 3)
  - Classified Newsletter (Box-folder 3)
  - ULI Washington/ Howard Johnson (Box-folder 3)
  - ULI WA: Port Ludlow 10/25, 1996 (Box-folder 3)
  - LI, 1995 (Box-folder 3)
  - ULI: Washington, 1994 (Box-folder 3)
  - ULI Washington, 1992 (Box-folder 3)
  - ULI Washington, 1998 (Box-folder 3)
  - Leadership Conference, 1991 (Box-folder 3)
  - VTI Instructor Survey (Box-folder 3)
  - WSFT Leg Com, 1970 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Legislation, 1965 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT, 1947 (Box-folder 3)
  - VTI Survey 4-90 (Box-folder 3)
  - Wakeup Call newsletter, 1982/1983 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Executive Board, 1989/1990 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT Executive Board, 1985 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT and AHE PT Faculty Rally, Feb. 1998 (Box-folder 3)
  - WFT misc (Box-folder 3)
  - Constitutions, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Constitutions, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4)
  - Constitutions, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 4)
  - Constitutions, 1970-1989 (Box-folder 4)
  - Extra Copies of Material on Four Year Faculty in Nation (Box-folder 4)
  - APT Project File (Box-folder 4)
  - Grays Harbor C.C. (Box-folder 4)
  - Everett (Box-folder 4)
  - Pierce College (Box-folder 4)
  - Counselor Staff (Box-folder 4)
  - Equity Packet, 1998 (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Survey (Box-folder 4)
  - Constituencies: Part Time (Box-folder 4)
  - Technical College Council (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Caucus, 1992 (Box-folder 4)
  - Faculty Seminars, 2001 (Box-folder 4)
  - NCSL, 1997 (Box-folder 4)
  - NCSL, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Contingent Worker, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Ergonomics Rule and Safety, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - AFLCIO UI Advisory Committee, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Pension Work Group (Box-folder 4)
  - PEPC, 1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Retirement System Three (Box-folder 4)
  - Updates on TIA/CREF, 1996 (Box-folder 4)
  - Retirement, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4)
  - Labor Law Update (Box-folder 4)
  - Post Tenure Evaluation (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Pro-Rata bill, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Session Fliers, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Labor Board Members (Box-folder 4)
  - SBCTC and Legislative Material, 1993 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Session, 2001 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Priorities and Fliers, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - Budget Conference, 1995 (Box-folder 4)
  - Pension Bill (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Misc, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - Increments, 2006 (Box-folder 4)
  - Performance Contract (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Performance Contract, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Bills (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Bill, 1996 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Tuition Fee Waiver bills (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Program, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Issues, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Equity Comp (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative, 2001 (Box-folder 4)
  - Charter Schools, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Higher Ed Legislative, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - SERS Optional (Box-folder 4)
  - Shared Tenure, 1992 (Box-folder 4)
  - Housing Allowance, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - Accountability, 2001 (Box-folder 4)
  - Vocational Certification, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - Books and Materials, 2006 (Box-folder 4)
  - Sick Leave Bill, 2006 (Box-folder 4)
  - Part Time Sick Leave, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Agenda, 2001 (Box-folder 4)
  - RnD Tax Exemptions, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - Higher Ed, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Unemployment Comp Cases (Box-folder 4)
  - August 4-9 Leg Conf in Philadelphia (Box-folder 4)
  - Bus Driver bill (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Session, 1998 (Box-folder 4)
  - Governor’s Task Force on Higher Ed (Box-folder 4)
  - General Legislative Program (Box-folder 4)
  - Work Certificates and Photos (Box-folder 4)
  - General Legislative Program (Box-folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action I-200 (Box-folder 4)
  - Work Force Training, 1988 (Box-folder 4)
  - Higher Ed TIA/CREF, 1996 (Box-folder 4)
  - UI Labor Caucus (Box-folder 4)
  - UI Staff (Box-folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 4)
  - AFT/WA old misc (Box-folder 4)
  - Staff work on council responsibilities (Box-folder 4)
  - Staff Meeting, 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Staff Material, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Staff Issues (Box-folder 4)
  - WFT Correspondence (Box-folder 4)
  - AFT WSU (Box-folder 4)
  - Classified Council Issues, 1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Retirees (Box-folder 4)
  - AFT/WA E Board Strategic Planning (Box-folder 4)
  - WFT/WEA Merger Talks (Box-folder 4)
  - Merger Talks (Box-folder 4)
  - Spotlight, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - AFT WA (Box-folder 4)
  - Community College Council, 1995 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Program, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - Convention Resolutions, 1995 (Box-folder 4)
  - Convention, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Convention, 1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Program, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legislative Program, 1993 (Box-folder 4)
  - UFWF, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - UofW Organizing, 2002 (Box-folder 4)
  - UofW Conference (Box-folder 4)
  - UFWF Strategy (Box-folder 4)
  - World Trade Organization Rally, 1999 (Box-folder 4)
  - Fliers & Handouts, 2003 (Box-folder 4)
  - Thank you for COPE Contribution (Box-folder 4)
  - TA Collective Bargaining (Box-folder 4)
  - R-55 (Box-folder 4)
  - COPE Committee, 2006 (Box-folder 4)
  - COPE Endorsement, 2004 (Box-folder 4)
  - COPE Pledge Drive, 2005 (Box-folder 4)
  - Initiative 2000 (Box-folder 4)
  - Legisletter, 1999 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1998 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1997 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1996 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1995 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1994 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1993 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1992 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1991 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 5)
  - Legisletter (Box-folder 5)
  - Misc (Box-folder 5)
  - Evelyn Rieder, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 5)
  - WFT College Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5)
  - PEMCO, 1993 (Box-folder 5)
  - Misc Corr R. Carlstrom/E Rieder, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 5)
  - WFT Carlstrom, Roger misc (Box-folder 5)
  - Save Our College campaign (Box-folder 5)
  - Part Time, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 5)
  - Part Time Task Force (Box-folder 5)
  - Part Time Survey (Box-folder 5)
  - Keith Hoeller (Box-folder 5)
  - Part Time Rally (Box-folder 5)
  - Legal Case misc, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 5)
  - PNW Labor College certificate (Box-folder 5)
  - Bus Driver Assault Bill (Box-folder 5)
  - WA Teacher, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 5)
  - WFT Local officer, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 5)
  - Resolution, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 5)
  - Ron Bell/Susan Levy (Box-folder 5)
  - Retirees (Box-folder 5)
  - Constitution, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 5)
  - Executive Bd minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 5)
  - Executive Bd, 2000 (Box-folder 5)
  - Executive Bd minutes, 2002 (Box-folder 5)
  - Executive Bd, 2001 (Box-folder 5)
  - AFT grants, 1993 (Box-folder 5)
  - AFT/NEA Project File (Box-folder 5)
  - AFT/NEA merger (Box-folder 5)
  - Equity Campaign, 2000 (Box-folder 5)
  - Equity Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5)
  - Lobby Day, 1999 (Box-folder 5)
  - Correspondence misc (Box-folder 5)
  - E Board minutes, 2000 (Box-folder 5)